TYPHOON FAMILY
Can you put your eyes on the line?
What's wrong?
You scared?
You have to swear
to leave us alone
once you get 100 million won.
What's wrong?
You scared?
What's your name?
That's none of your business.
I'm just a trader…
from Typhoon Trading.
DEBT ACKNOWLEDGEMENT FORM
COLLATERAL: TWO EYEBALLS
Damn it!
This is tough.
Shall I…
start doing some business?
EPISODE 6
THE LEGEND OF AMBITION
Tae-poong!
Hey!
Hey, Tae-poong! You punk.
How the heck could you just run off
and leave me with this guy?
Gosh.
I got scared after seeing a loan shark
for the first time in my life.
Scared?
If you get scared twice,
you'll level the whole damn block!
-What now?
-What?
I'm sure he's thanking you.
No one on earth is like you.
You should've come yesterday.
I was beaten up badly yesterday.
Darn it! I'm so done with this!
Jeez.
Yesterday?
This is too much.
Why did I get caught up in this?
Hey, let's at least drop him off
at a hospital before we go.
I can't do this.
One, two, three!
Can you take me home
instead of to the hospital?
-Here?
-The lights are on.
One moment, please.
I got…
How do I look?
I don't look like
I've been beaten up, do I?
Even people about 100 m away from you
can clearly tell you were beaten up.
-You're all swollen.
-Yes.
Is that so?
That's not good.
By any chance,
do you have any makeup I can use?
I don't. I'm not wearing any makeup.
I may not look like it,
but I never use foundation.
Don't be so harsh, and let me borrow some.
I can probably scrape some off your face.
How dare you? I'll break your fingers.
Is she your daughter?
She's not asleep, is she?
I can't spend the night out tonight.
What do I do now?
-Give me a moment. Let's see.
-What?
If you had a kid,
you should've just said so.
-Careful.
-It must hurt.
-Be gentle. Okay.
-I'll put thick makeup on you.
Daddy!
Oh, gosh.
I'm so sorry
for leaving you here all alone, Bo-ram.
It's okay. I'm a brave girl.
Anyway, what is this?
Christmas has passed long ago.
I wanted to give you a present,
so I came here on Rudolph. Here it is.
Who did you take after
and become so smart?
-I took after my daddy.
-Hey, don't say that.
Do you want to blow this out, Bo-ram?
You're Uncle Crazy Tae-poong, right?
Uncle Crazy Tae-poong?
Yes, that's me, Uncle Crazy Tae-poong.
-You're good-looking.
-I am?
Thank you.
Thank you so much for this.
Sure.
Should we eat cake?
-Yes.
-Let's eat it.
Let's eat cake. Let me bring some dishes.
Daddy, this is so cute.
-Is it?
-Yes.
Hello?
Were you asleep?
No.
Are you done with work?
Yes, I'm taking the bus back now.
Good work.
Well…
Ms. Oh.
Yes, please speak.
Well…
Is there no sentiment in this work?
-What?
-You know, sentiment.
Like love, justice,
or faith, something of that sort.
Never mind.
Don't I sound like a fool for asking this?
Those can't even be seen.
Mr. Kang.
Will you look up at the sky?
Do you see the stars?
I don't.
It's way too cloudy.
Does that mean they don't exist
just because you don't see them now?
You're right.
Please return safely.
Why are you smiling?
-What?
-Why are you smiling alone?
Don't mind me. Oh, right.
Turn on the TV.
Let's watch the New Year's bell ceremony.
That ceremony happens every single year.
Why do you have to see it?
You always want to watch it!
TICKETS
Wait…
What?
EXPRESS BUS WINDOW CLOSED
FOR 1997 AS OF 23:00
-We're witnessing a historic moment.
-Telemarketing?
-We're at Bosingak for the ceremony.
-Make money while chatting?
Once the Bosingak Bell strikes 33 times…
-We will now welcome 1998.
-A skillful cook?
-There're 20 people from different fields.
-That's me.
-They'll help us ring the bell.
-What else?
Among them, there is a hero
who comforted us the most this year.
It's Coach Cha Bum-kun
of the national soccer team.
Look at you. Your handsome face is ruined.
We're about to say
goodbye to the awfully eventful 1997
as everyone here anticipates
and dreams of a better tomorrow.
May only warm laughter
and good things fill our new year.
Is that helpful?
-We're at Bosingak.
-This keeps moisture in my skin.
-It is full of passion here.
-Look.
I'm just hoping the bell rings soon.
-Grandma, they're striking the bell.
-Ten seconds left.
-Eight, seven, six…
-Five, four…
-…five, four,
-three, two, one…
-Don't eat it, Grandma! It's dirty!
Happy New Year, Grandma!
-Wonderful.
-You always get excited about that.
Why can't they hit it harder?
It's always a very low ding.
-It's so frustrating.
-It's cold.
1998 CALENDAR
HAPPY NEW YEAR
JANUARY
Did you eat a piece of cucumber?
The nights seemed
especially longer this winter.
The deeper the night is, the sooner
the sun will rise in the morning.
It was so nearby.
The sentiment.
Ms. Oh!
-You should've gone home to get some rest.
-No, I had a good night's sleep.
-Did you?
-Yes. Oh, right!
Were the products not there?
-It's okay. We just--
-No.
I got the products.
Over there.
There's quite a bit.
-A bit?
-Yes.
Yes, just a bit.
How many is a bit?
-It should be about five…
-Five hundred pairs?
More like 6,500.
Is this it? It's not as bad as I thought.
-It's that way, the back alley.
-Is that so?
-Is there coffee?
-What now?
I always have coffee in the morning.
Wait, how many pairs?
-Hey, we brought 7,000. Let's go.
-If not, I'll buy some.
-No, there's coffee around here.
-It's 7,000?
I like the brand Rich Aroma,
but you don't drink that.
I like that because I'm a fan
of the actor, Ahn Sung-ki.
-Are you?
-Yes.
It may seem like a lot,
but we can sell everything
in three months, right?
We're going to be rich now.
You must be out of your mind!
Ms. Oh!
The more I get to know coffee,
the more I become drawn
to this rich aroma.
Rich Aroma.
Coffee is best in the American style.
-What's the ratio?
-Two coffee, four sugar, and four cream.
Americans take their coffee sweet.
-Is that so?
-Stop complaining. It's past due.
Pay me back by tomorrow, you punk!
All these infantile punks
are talking total bullshit to me.
Infantile…
I have no idea what she just said.
CPU, 116 MB. Memory, 1.2 GB. Hard disk…
You're running low on the hard disk space.
-How did you know?
-I was formerly an engineer.
Did you major in engineering?
I went to the Maritime University,
not engineering.
Maritime University?
I studied ships and boats,
mostly large vessels, like Captain Nemo.
Captain Harlock is the best captain.
No, the best captain out there
is Spock of Star Trek.
Live long and prosper.
Do you know this?
-Of course, I do!
-What about this?
-How do you know this?
-I'm a huge fan of Star Trek.
-By any chance, are you on Cheonrian?
-Just a little.
It's great to meet you.
What now?
How is 500 the same as 7,000?
This is such an absurd amount.
Construction projects have stopped,
including the airport. Who'll buy those?
We should export those.
That's even harder to do
than selling domestically!
Why do you think that way?
This means we have more opportunities.
-Opportunities?
-Yes, opportunities.
Good luck with that opportunity then.
-Wait.
-Hey.
-Mi-seon!
-Wait…
I knew this would happen.
Hey, Mi-seon!
I've never seen
Ms. Oh that furious before.
Let me know if there's anything I can do.
Close the door and leave.
Shall we?
-Anyway, when will others come to work?
-This is everyone.
-This is it?
-Yes.
It's just Mr. Kang and Ms. Oh.
-What about you?
-Me?
I'm family.
A freeloader.
Family.
Freeloader.
SELF-INSPECTION
You must've been a rich lady
who used to live in Gangnam.
-Well, I just look rich.
-You're really bad.
You're so bad at your job.
I've run this factory for 20 years,
and you were the first assistant who left
after finishing a box of bandages.
Are you firing me?
Come half an hour early starting tomorrow.
Even if you do, you still won't finish
half of what others can.
What can I get with this?
Hey.
Do you work here?
Hey, do you want me
to make you something delicious?
In return, you have to keep a secret
between you and me.
A secret?
Does that upset you that much?
Why are you so upset?
Worried the company will go under?
Then come and work for me.
I'll pay you twice as much.
Mr. Kang made this decision by himself.
So what?
-Do you think he disregarded you?
-No.
Gosh, Mi-seon.
What did you lose?
Tae-poong lost everything
except for the name of the business.
What did you bet in this business
to act like you're equal to him?
Yes, what he did was wrong.
However, work is different.
SAVING ENERGY WILL TURN INTO ABUNDANCE
Gosh, come on.
Where did Ms. Oh go?
Yes?
-You should go if you're that worried.
-I'm not.
Anyway, are you sure about this?
-It gets freezing cold here.
-I even slept at the factory.
This feels like a hotel in comparison.
I think it'll be better
if you came home with me.
Gosh.
If I impose on you any more,
I won't be able to face you again.
I'll be fine. You should go.
Please use this if it gets colder.
You'll find what you need in the pantry.
Hey…
Never mind. Goodbye.
Good night.
-I'll turn the lights off.
-Okay.
So why do you work?
Be honest.
-For a man?
-No.
I work…
for my dream.
Your dream?
Dream.
-Make sure you achieve it.
-Okay.
-Move it.
-Right. I'm sorry.
-Goodbye, then.
-Bye.
Keep driving straight.
Ms. Oh!
Where have you been?
I was worried. Are you all right?
I'm not.
I'm sorry.
I promised not to make you mad, but…
Wait, I have to use that.
-What?
-My wish coupon.
Sorry?
WISH COUPON
I wish Ms. Oh wouldn't be mad… No.
I wish she would accept the apology
of Kang Tae-poong.
You can't take it back.
Fine.
But promise me
you'll never act on your own again.
I promise.
Jeez.
Is there anything else
you haven't told me yet?
Are you going to pull out
30,000 pairs of shoes tomorrow?
Goodness, hardly.
I have nothing like that now.
Well…
Actually, I…
Can you put your eyes on the line?
Leave us alone
once you get 100 million won.
I signed off my eyes to a loan shark--
One more thing.
You cannot get hurt.
That's all I need from you.
If you remain healthy and well,
I promise I won't flip out.
I'm sorry. What about your eyes?
I did a staring contest with a loan shark.
I see.
-Did you win?
-Yes, of course, I did.
-I never lose.
-Is that so?
Hey…
Never mind. Goodbye.
Ms. Oh, you should go first.
I left something in the office.
-You should go, okay?
-Yes, okay.
-Thanks a lot.
-Sure.
Be careful. Don't run! Good grief.
I just told him not to run.
Oh, man.
Darn it. Come on!
SEOUL EXPRESS BUS TERMINAL
Mr. Park.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Park!
I knew it.
It's not even for Pusan, but Wando Island.
Wando Island?
Come with me.
-Mr. Park!
-Get him!
I'll pay for him later!
Darn it!
Jeez. Come on.
Seriously?
I was the fastest runner in my class!
-Hey!
-Wait!
-Let go of me, you punk.
-No!
-We need to talk.
-Let go.
Let go of me!
So? Where are you going?
I couldn't ask you before,
but come with me, Mr. Kang.
There are so many isles
down in the Wando Island area
that people can't find you
once you decide to hide.
The world would've changed
after we spent a few years there.
Why would I hide?
I didn't do anything wrong.
My goodness.
I saw that Typhoon Trading
is also about to go under.
So why did you get so nosy?
I thought you had some money
when you blurted out something
about 100 million won or whatever.
But all you have is that one female staff.
How is that a decent business?
At the very least,
I had 50 people on my payroll,
and I still couldn't make it.
Exporting?
Do you think I haven't thought of that?
We can't compete
with China in this day and age!
They sell whatever they have
at less than half our price in the market.
How will you sell those in three months
and make 100 million won?
Forget everything else.
What about Bo-ram?
I sent her to my wife's family.
She'll be safer there.
What about your staff at Shoe Park?
So? What about them
who're working hard in this cold season?
What can I do?
Pusan is full of the unemployed.
What about Shoe Park?
What about 30 years of your life?
What about your patents?!
Mr. Kang.
Do you know
what those loan sharks are like?
You saw me that day.
They run their business
by selling people's bodies.
I'd rather die
than to get dragged back there.
Gosh, then just go and die!
What?
But before you do that,
we should try to sell these first!
You haven't tried anything yet!
Right? I'm going to sell these!
Are you not confident? But I am!
Confidence?
Confidence isn't enough to pull this off.
Everyone is shutting down
construction sites.
And you can't make 100 million won
by selling these to China or Saudi Arabia.
Who will you sell them to?
Where will you sell them?
That's…
IMPORTED FLOWERS FROM EUROPE
-Over there. Look.
-Where?
It went by.
What went by?
Ready?
-Yes, I'm ready.
-Okay.
Mr. Kang, you can just walk up on the top.
Get ready.
Press the red button.
Don't worry. I'm a veteran
in the Cheonrian Quiz Room.
What did Mak-dong
give to Mi-ae in Green Fish?
-A scarf.
-I knew it.
-And the color?
-Red.
Why did you suddenly jump off?
I haven't even taken the lens cover off.
-What?
-One more time.
Jump off after I say, "Ready, cue."
All right. Here we go.
I haven't even pressed the record button.
What's with you?
-Give that to me. I'll do it better.
-No, this is my personal camcorder.
KITT, let's do it over.
-We can do this.
-From the top.
Get ready.
All right. Get ready.
-Cue!
-Shoe Park Pro!
-Did it go well?
-Yes!
Hey, are you hurt? You're hurt!
Let me see.
You're bleeding.
-Let me get some medicine.
-Why didn't you press stop sooner?
-You ended up getting him hurt.
-People can make mistakes.
It's all right. Great job.
He did a great job. Don't be harsh.
-Just hold on for a second.
-Okay.
-One moment.
Hold on a little more.
-You pressed it.
-I'm sorry.
-You need to be careful.
-Okay, I'll be careful.
Aren't you hungry?
-I'm starving.
-Right?
-Buns.
-I got some steamed buns.
I really like this flavor.
Thank you so much.
Wait, don't you think
the size difference is way too big?
I like these too.
-Eat up. Thanks.
-Okay, enjoy.
It's good.
-You know.
-Yes?
Do we have to try so hard
with the video and all?
I want to show them
our goods and our good taste
since we're traders.
Just wait. You'll live to see a day
when people watch everything in videos.
People won't be able to resist buying
our product when they see it.
I envy you for the ability
to instantly think like that.
What do you mean?
You'll have to perform
the most difficult task.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
TYPHOON TRADING
You cannot compromise your safety.
-I'm going to sell these at full price.
-How?
UNITED STATES
EUROPE
Like this.
Are these all for America?
What's inside?
Promotional material for safety shoes.
-Let's end everything here.
-No, look.
The key is the payroll cost.
-The payroll cost?
-Yes.
You saw those roses
at the Express Bus Terminal, right?
They came from Europe,
so there must be the logistics cost,
but those are expensive as is!
-It was nice meeting you.
-Why? Because their wage is higher!
-Please don't leave--
-Don't hold me back.
-What are you doing?
-Hello, sir. I have a brochure.
I'm not a solicitor. It's just a brochure.
You can't leave these here. Please leave.
All right.
Asia still has much lower labor costs,
but it's exploding with manpower.
Safety laws still aren't enough.
What do you think
it's like in America or Europe?
They'll have to pay medical expenses
and recruit new people.
And if things go haywire,
they'll end up with lawsuits.
In such times, these shoes
will come in handy and prevent everything.
FOR THE HIGHEST QUALITY
It comes with five patents.
This place is so clean.
It's nice.
Ms. Oh.
-Ms. Oh.
-Yes?
Did you not get enough sleep?
I was too nervous.
I had to memorize English lines.
One second.
Are you nervous?
I'm not nervous at all.
I guess it's a difficult task,
but you're the best trader in our company.
All done.
You got this.
I got this.
-Let's go.
-Okay. Thanks.
Hello.
I'm leaving first.
See you tomorrow.
-Did I keep you waiting?
-No, not for too long.
Aren't you cold?
-Are you cold?
-I am.
My hands are freezing.
One second.
What? Why do you always give me this?
Because I can't hold your hand yet.
But this gets cold quickly.
-It's okay. I have more.
-Forget it.
This way?
This way.
I have to get back to work now.
Okay. Bye.
Wait.
Can you leave me a message?
I think I'll want to hear your voice.
Well…
I'll think about it.
I'll go now, then. What?
You know,
do you think
they'll call and sign the deal?
Of course.
And you did such a great job today.
I'm not sure.
-I feel too uneasy.
-It's all right.
This is just our beginning.
-You're right.
-Oh, my.
She's smiling. Does she like Tae-poong?
Wait. I know that voice.
Right. I had a present for you.
I almost forgot.
-Let me get it.
-A present?
It better not be
something like paper cranes.
I made 999 cranes,
and you have to make the last one.
That way, your wish will come true.
My wish is to marry someone rich.
Sure. Make a wish and let me know.
I can be the man you want.
Don't bring this
when you come next time.
What are you doing? Oh, my.
See you tomorrow.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
And the day after that!
And next week and next year!
Let's keep seeing each other!
Good night!
What's going on?
-Is this a special day?
-It's not a special day.
I just made some side dishes. That's all.
-Eat up.
-Goodness.
Wait.
-What happened to your hands?
-Oh, nothing.
I'm just not used to doing chores at home.
Even if that's the case, how…
It's good.
-Be careful.
-Eat up, okay?
It's good, so eat up.
Eat up, Beom. Take a big bite.
-You should eat, Mom. He's doing fine.
-I'm eating too.
Here.
I'm a pretty good cook.
-Eat up.
-Okay.
EXPORT TO EUROPE
LIST OF COMPANIES
USA
EXPORTS TO EUROPE INCREASE BY 10%
Hey, something's coming.
-"Ecnarf…"
-To France.
-Right. To France?
-France.
What's this?
-It's for foot volleyball.
-Jeez.
-It's this one, Mr. Kang.
-Right.
Hello, you've reached Typhoon Trading.
Yes, thank you! Goodbye!
What did they say?
I think we got a deal.
-We did?
-We got it! My gosh!
-Yes, we got it!
I don't know how!
My heart is racing so fast!
-Yes!
-We got it!
My gosh. We did it!
Dad, I sold something for the first time.
Why does this feel so good?
Worthwhile…
SHARING GOOD NEWS
Worthwhile.
Mr. Researcher.
Some snacks for you.
Thanks.
Goodbye, then.
TYPHOON TRADING
These are the documents
for export permits,
so give it
to the shipping company or whatever.
Okay, then.
These will leave in two days?
I don't even work here,
so you can't make me work.
Five hours of time online.
Let me know after you file it by 6:00 p.m.
-I'll page you if any problem arises.
-Okay.
I'll be there after inspecting
the 2,000 pairs in the Hwaseong factory.
-Was it Hongshin Company?
-Yes, she's throwing a party.
Do you want to join us, Mr. Bae?
No, I also have a crazy party to attend.
-See you tonight.
-See you.
-Are you starting now?
-Yes, please check the time.
It was five hours.
You have until 1:10 p.m.
Let's drop ten minutes
and start at 8:00 a.m.
What?
What do you mean,
you can't load our shoes now?
Are you kidding me?
-Where's Tae-poong now?
-He went straight to the shipping company.
This is driving me crazy.
What do you mean the shipping company
canceled the shipment?
What? Typhoon Trading is on a blacklist?
Have you lost your mind?
ANNOUNCEMENT: SHIPPING BLACKLIST
-Why are we blacklisted?
-I don't know the reason.
These are to leave in two days.
You can't just cancel it like this.
We just received an order,
so we don't have a choice.
We won't have enough time
to find a new shipping company.
Can you please help us out?
I'm begging you.
There's no use in doing this.
I can't help you. I don't have any power.
Who's this punk?
-Hello, sir.
-Why is this fraud here?
What's going on?
Mr. Vice CEO.
Do you remember Typhoon Trading
I mentioned earlier?
He's the guy.
Last time, he scammed us
with the quantity,
and this time,
he even stole products from loan sharks.
No, sir.
I'm not sure what you heard from him,
but we didn't do that.
Please let us load the products
as you have promised,
and then we can undo the misunderstanding.
Why don't we head
to the raw fish restaurant?
I made a reservation
at a phenomenal place.
It won't do your ears any good
to hear out a sham like him.
Mr. Vice CEO,
please hear me out just once.
I would've been in big trouble
if it hadn't been for you, Mr. Pyo.
Where's the restaurant again?
-Let me lead the way.
-Goodbye, sir!
-Let's go, sir.
-Where is it?
Goodbye, sir.
Will you leave now? Goodness gracious.
You also know the punk
at Pyo Merchant Marine, right?
He's just no good.
Yes.
I talked to Ms. Oh.
But it looks like
there's no way around this.
I looked up ways to ship it via plane,
but that'll cost much more.
I can't believe these jerks
stopped you from shipping these out!
Where are you going? Hey!
Where are you going, Tae-poong?
What's he going to do?
What will he do with these?
This is fun.
Jeez. That startled me.
What an idiot.
What do you think?
It's stronger than your head, isn't it?
I really love these.
You crazy punk.
Didn't you know I was crazy?
You know how people would come out on TV
and say things like, "This work
or this product is like my child"?
I never knew what that meant.
But these feel that way to me.
It's the first ever product I've sold.
They feel like my own children.
So what, you punk?
Do whatever else you can.
But the next time,
what breaks won't be this window.
It'll be
right up here.
And Jeon Sa-dok loses.
Let's go, my baby.
Jeon Sa-dok loses?
Darn it!
This is bad.
Those should've been loaded by now.
Even if we find another company,
Pyo won't let it happen.
Mr. Park will be devastated
if he finds out.
So what's your plan?
Of course…
I do have a plan.
What's with you?
Why do you seem so off?
This isn't water! It's alcohol!
Hey, this is alcohol!
What are you talking about?
Oh, my.
Hey, I left alcohol in there
to wash tripe.
How did it end up there?
You know, I always have a plan.
Now, listen.
I'll take the shoes and tie everything up.
-Tie them up?
-Tie them up.
Then I'll put them on my huge shoulders.
-I'll do that.
-Okay.
I'll swim freestyle or breaststroke
to cross the Pacific.
Then I'll do the backstroke
to cross the Atlantic.
My goodness!
I was a former swimmer
at the YWCY baby sports team.
You held out for a while.
Jeez!
Use your legs a little, you punk.
When did you get here, Mr. Park?
Did you hear the news?
What can he do?
-He did his best.
-Let's go.
-Ms. Jung.
-Yes?
How long does it take
to get to Wando Island from here?
Wando Island? Why?
We should save this young man.
I'm telling you, use your legs!
We're almost there.
-Where?
-Pull yourself together!
I've walked for too long.
Gosh.
The lights are on.
Is Bo-ram still up waiting for you?
Thank you
for showing concern for Bo-ram too.
Bo-ram!
Wait.
-Sir, why are you doing this?
-Why didn't you come sooner, you idiot?
What are you doing?
You're late.
Don't touch her.
-She'll wake up.
-Do you like kids?
I don't.
Hey, how dare you come here?
Ms. Jung.
Am I not allowed to be here?
I like it here.
So you couldn't load your stuff?
What about my money?
Have you been tailing me?
I know everything
that's happening in Pusan.
You know what I like?
Those sparkly eyes of yours.
They seem so familiar.
Was it here?
They'll be mine in a month.
Keep them safe.
What's he talking about?
Ms. Oh.
Who's she?
I am Senior Staff Oh Mi-seon
of Typhoon Trading.
Is the girl yours?
May I ask you to elaborate
on what you just said?
DEBT ACKNOWLEDGEMENT FORM
COLLATERAL: TWO EYEBALLS
And you're serious?
I never tell jokes.
Okay.
Ms. Oh.
Wait up, Ms. Oh.
-Where are you going at this hour?
-To Seoul. I'll find a way.
I'm sorry. I can explain.
-I was going to tell you, but--
-Mr. Kang.
Are you serious?
What do you mean?
Do you think everything we're doing
and have done is a joke?
Are you saying the work I did was a joke?
It wasn't?
Then what were you thinking
when you signed that form?
-Did it make any sense to you?
-I get what you mean.
But Mr. Park was in real danger!
So what?
Did you pity him?
Did you want to help him and look cool?
All right. Everything's great.
But you should've done that personally.
You went there to find our product
as the CEO of Typhoon Trading!
And what? Did you go there to play a hero?
Play a hero?
If you're going to be emotional,
there's no point to doing all this.
No.
It's not just about money.
What was it like after Mr. Kang passed?
How could you sign yourself away again?
Then Typhoon Trading and I
would've lost the CEO twice.
Has it crossed your mind? Was it so easy?
How am I going to trust
a CEO like that and continue to work here?
We're not a rescue organization.
We're a trading company!
You have no idea
what's the most important to us.
What do you think
is the most important to us?
We're a trading company,
so it's making money,
paying off debts, and saving our business.
My mom keeps making me bulgogi,
although I don't bring her a penny.
Everything you said was right.
I'm not good enough,
and I'm too emotional.
But I've never considered this a joke.
Actually…
Actually, it's difficult and scary.
But, Ms. Oh,
no matter how hard and scary it is,
we can't turn a blind eye to someone
who's dying before us
and begging for help.
I'm sorry for not giving you enough faith.
But I'll always make the same choice.
I can't help it.
This is who I am.
Let's go back to Seoul.
Do you know where you're going?
I don't know anything.
I don't even know what's important.
If I say
we should walk over to the lights,
will you think that's too emotional?
You're holding grudges now?
-What now?
-Just come.
CAUTION: SLIPPERY FLOOR
WEAR ANTI-SLIP BOOTS
Look who it is. Aren't you two from Seoul?
-Hello.
-Hey, there.
What brings you here in the dead of night?
No reason.
Did you two fight?
-No.
-Yes.
-You're right.
-How adorable.
No, we're not.
Look at you two.
What's this fish?
These are mackerels,
and these are horse mackerels.
Hey, Captain!
Great work today.
The horse mackerels are quite fresh.
Captain, where do these come from?
You wouldn't know where in the vast sea.
It's the sea near our country.
But they must've swam here
from quite a distance,
somewhere in the Pacific.
Hey, Jeong-gun! Come on.
Excuse me, Captain.
By the way, how far can this boat go?
Can it reach Mexico?
-Mexico?
-Yes.
If it ends up in Mexico,
it'll be a shipwreck.
But there are fishing boats
that travel to South America.
You'll find
deep-sea fishing vessels over there.
They don't just go to South America.
They go to Alaska, Europe,
and all around the globe.
Why?
-Do you want to get on one?
-No, not us.
Just forget it.
Once onboard,
you're out there for two years minimum.
By any chance,
do you know where I can find such a ship?
That must be it.
FV IMAGIN
Hi, is the captain here?
Captain! Sir!
What do you want?
Hello.
My name is Kang Tae-poong
of Typhoon Trading.
We wanted to ask you for a favor, sir.
Do you load different items on your ship,
such as shoes?
We have 5,000 safety shoes
that have to go.
Can you ship them to Mexico?
Did he just say yes?
-I think so.
-Right?
Boys.
-Did it work?
-I think so.
What? Why?
-Goodness!
-What is it?
-Wait! Why?
-Why?
THE LEGEND OF AMBITION
TYPHOON FAMILY
Why do you make me worried sick?
You punk!
Do you know how much damage you caused?
Do you have what it takes
to take Kang Tae-poong down?
What are you doing?
I want to sell this,
but I don't know where to begin.
We'll start exporting to Thailand now.
I didn't think it seemed right
for Ms. Oh Mi-seon to be in sales.
But Ms. Oh is Typhoon Trading's trader.
And when you smile, you're beautiful.
I think I like you.